MAKSYM KOVAL FRONT-END DEVELOPER

GitHub | In LinkedIn | Facebook | +1506-235-5417 | maksim6167@gmail.com

SUMMARY:

Web developer with a passion for web application development. Experienced in the development, support and maintenance of web applications. Results oriented team player. Constantly learning and improving my skills in writing clean, readable and efficient code using SOLID and DRY principles.

TECHNIAL SKILLS

Programming Skills

TypeScript, JavaScript/ES6+, HTML, CSS/SCSS, Ajax

Libraries

React, Redux, Bootstrap, Material UI, Ant Design, Axios

Web Services

REST API

Testing

Jest, StoryBook, Postman

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Freelance

Front-End Developer | April, 2021 - Present

I am creating an application from scratch that can be used as a social network or can be adapted to a forum. The application is developed on React + Redux. Development is based on functional components, React Hooks and other modern tools. For requests to the server, the Axios library is used. The application is currently under development and is constantly being updated.

Freelance

Front-End Developer | April, 2021 - October 2021

- Created WordPress plugin and sett up a personal account for "Childhood" website.
- Built a landing page from scratch for a local transport company, "UBER Partners". The website developed according to the BEM methodology using the Bootstrap library.
- Created of website functionality for "IRWAS windows". Installed and configured the Slick Slider plugin.
- Built a landing page from scratch for "RunSmart" according to modern standards HTML5
 CSS3 / SCSS. Installed the Mailer plugin to send emails without a server.

EDUCATION:

2021 - 2022 | IT-INCUBATOR Bootcamp

Front - End Developer

React, Redux, TypeScript, JavaScript, Axios, Material UI, Ant Design, REST API, Formik, Jest, Postman, Storybook

2020 - 2022 | Udemy, Codeacademy

Web Developer

HTML, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript, WebPack, Babel, Git

2007 - 2015 | Prydniprovska State Academy of Civil Engineering and Architecture

Mechanical Engineer